yourhcg.com 2010-04-16

# Your HCG | Privacy Policy

Effective Janurary 1st, 2009

Your HCG is committed to protecting your privacy and utilizing technology that gives you the most powerful, safe, on-line experience available. We want to assure you that when Your HCG asks for consumer information, it's done with the goal of improving our relationship.

The following statements will help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard information you provide to Body Solutions Rx.

**_Internet Specific Information_**

Information Collection and Use 

When you browseYour HCG website, you do so without revealing your identity. Personal information, including email address, is not collected without your awareness. For each visitor to our website, our servers recognize the website you came from.

In the order capture process, Your HCG may track the order preferences of visitors to our website. Information tracked and retained byYour HCG is generic and not individually identifiable. This is accomplished through cookies. Cookies Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. A cookie may contain information (such as unique session ID), that is used to track the pages of the sites you’ve visited. We use cookies but do not store personally identifiable information in your cookies.Your HCGx Website uses cookies in order to improve your shopping experience. This information helps us serve you better by keeping track of your order as you shop at our site and it helps us by improving our site design.

Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can use the majority of the features within our sites. 

Identifying Information You Choose to Provide 

At times,Your HCGmay request that you voluntarily supply personal information for purposes such as correspondence, site registration, making a purchase, participating in an on-line survey or employment opportunities. If you elect to participate, Your HCG may require personally identifiable information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, bank information, credit card information or email address. When you submit personal information to Your HCG you understand and agree that as allowed by contract Your HCG may access, store and use your information. Information you provide will be safeguarded to strict standards of security and confidentiality. BecauseYour HCG recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of the information you choose to provide, we do not share email addresses.

Security of Information 

Security measures are in place on theYour HCG website to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We offer industry-standard security measures available through your web browser. When you are on our website, the information you provide is encrypted and scrambled en route and decoded once it reaches Your HCG. Please remember that email, which is different from the encrypted sessions above, is not secure. Therefore, we ask that you do not send confidential information such as social security or account numbers to us via unsecured email. Such communications should be sent to us by postal mail or phone.

Your HCG takes steps to require that its vendors, consultants, suppliers, and contractors we hire observe our Privacy Policy with respect to security and the collection, use and exchange of our consumers’ individual consumer information. They are expected to abide by the Privacy Policy when conducting work for us.

Children Visiting our website

Our website is directed at adult consumers and guests. However, children may access our website and provide information. They may request information concerning our products and services and attempt to order certain products and services. Should children access our website, we are confident that parents will not judge any of the information provided as objectionable for viewing. If you are under 18, you may use the Your HCG website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

Other Websites Linked to Your HCG

Your HCG is not responsible for the content or information practices employed by sites linked to or from our website. In most cases, links to non-Your HCG websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of theYour HCGwebsite. 

**_General Business Practices_**

Disclosure of Individual Consumer Information

We are committed to protecting your private information.Your HCG uses the information collected from you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. Your HCG may also use your information to communicate with you about products, services, and promotions in the future. For the purposes of check verification and fraud prevention,Your HCG will provide data about our consumers to reputable reference sources and clearinghouse services. The information we gather may be used to protect consumers, employees and property against fraud, theft or abuse; to conduct industry or consumer surveys; and to maintain good consumer relations.

Your HCG does not share email addresses, or any other information with vendors outside out company.

Choice to Opt-Out

Your HCG provides consumers the opportunity to opt-out of receiving unsolicited mail from Your HCG. You may opt-out by calling 1-801-953-3049 and expressing your request. You may also make this request by any other communication option listed below underYour HCG

Identifying Information You Choose to Provide

At times, Your HCG may request that you voluntarily supply personal information for purposes such as correspondence, website registration, making a purchase, participating in an on-line survey or employment opportunities. If you elect to participate, Your HCG may require personally identifiable information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, bank information, credit card information or email address. When you submit personal information to Your HCG you understand and agree thatYour HCG and our affiliates may access, store and use your information. Information you provide will be safeguarded to strict standards of security and confidentiality. BecauseYour HCG recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of the information you choose to provide, we do not share email addresses with other companies.

Correct/Update/Access

Your HCG is committed to ensuring that the information we obtain and use about consumers is accurate. You can help us maintain the accuracy of information previously provided or information we may have collected by informing us of changes or modifications through the **Contacting Your HCG** methods described below, or by calling 1-801-953-3049 Your HCG service representatives are trained to answer consumer questions, and to give consumers reasonable access to the information we have about them.

Enforcement

Periodically, our operations and business practices are reviewed for compliance with corporate policies and procedures governing the confidentiality of information. These reviews are conducted by internal staff, internal auditors who report directly to the Board of Directors, external auditing and accounting firms and government regulators. Included in these self-assessments and examinations are reviews of the controls and safeguards related to consumer privacy described in our Privacy Policy.

Privacy Policy Changes

We may change our privacy policy at any time. Any changes to the privacy and security policy will be posted on this website so that you are aware of the information we collect, how we use it, as well as the latest updates on how we maintain the secure portions of our website.

Your Acceptance of These Terms

By purchasing products or services from Your HCG x or using theYour HCGwebsite, you consent to the Privacy Statement forYour HCG. If you do not agree with this policy, please do not purchase from us and do not use our site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to Your HCG website following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.

Contacting Your HCG

E-mail:jaime@yourhcg.com
